{
    "id": "50e76f3cf9944b4a8b36531dcbc53a4e",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is important to abide .............................. the rules and regulations.",
            "description": "To abide by a rule is to respect it.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3ddc5dcd1b4f474b89ade9cd909a8297"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope you can account ........................... the money you spent on that expensive vacation.",
            "description": "To account for is to explain.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1cb08237c258427b9c78166d0c6ea19c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her explanations just do not add ............................",
            "description": "When explanations add up, they make sense.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d90ef50211cd4270a9493a1677f1e3a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man advised me ............................. walking alone after sunset.",
            "description": "To advise against something is to recommend not doing it.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "against",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87ace000269f43359e5792fd22c824ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you agree .................................. the opinion that education should be free for all?",
            "description": "When you agree with something, you have the same opinion.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "aa245ae5f03549339a038990dcc46ac0"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must allow .................................. potential problems that can delay the completion of the project.",
            "description": "To allow for something is to take that into consideration.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "90488db87992407f90a747c589e61a1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The idea of spending an afternoon at the beach just does not appeal ............................... me.",
            "description": "If something appeals to you, you find it attractive or interesting. ",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a562cf9cf06e4f529b7b6a5393e9cd81"
        },
        {
            "question": "When the child saw the snake, he backed ................................... in fright.",
            "description": "To back away is to move backwards in fear.",
            "answers": [
                "down",
                "away",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7cb537d95b2e42b2a046e39c902ac3b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The protesters forced the government to back .................................. on its attempts to demolish the old fort.",
            "description": "To back down is to withdraw or concede defeat.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cca32ce8ec444346ae25b616a0c3e051"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was in trouble, there was no one to back me ................................",
            "description": "To back somebody up is to give them support.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "15cdc5e8deb34e1495856c0e421a6db2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you blowing ................................. at me when it is not my fault?",
            "description": "To blow up at somebody is to get angry with them.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e4a27fa2b0e46beb6bb79f4f20a002e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Riots have broken ................................ in parts of the country.",
            "description": "When a riot breaks out, it starts suddenly.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e7fbb8a2900d48c89d0cff1c8700965e"
        }
    ]
}